One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Who found him first? Please let us question them!
第一発見者は誰ですか？ 質問させてください！
Are there any suspects?
犯人は何者なんですか？
Any connection to the Franky House collapse?
フランキーハウス壊滅と 何かつながりがあるんでしょうか？
Can we get a statement?!
何かコメントを！
Any new developments?!
最新の情報をお願いします
Hey, did you hear about what happened at Shipyard Island?
おい聞いたか？ ゆうべの造船島の事件
Is he really dead?
死んだってのは本当なのか？
Franky must have done it!
フランキーがやったに違いないわ
This happened because they don't lock him up!
あんなヤツ野放しにしてるから こんなことになったのよ
Well, it could very well have been any of the pirates who visit the shipyard.
いや　造船所を出入りする 海賊の仕業って線も強いんだ
So this is where you guys were.
ここにいたのか
We went to the trouble of getting a room, but no one's even using it.
せっかく宿取ったのに部屋に誰もいねえ
I guess none of you could sleep, huh?
みんなそろって眠れてねえんだろ
Where's Luffy?
ルフィは？
Over there.
あそこ
Where'd you go, Sanji?
サンジ　どこ行ってたんだ？
Hm? I kept a lookout at the rocky cape all night just in case Robin came back.
ん？夜中じゅう岩場の岬を見張ってた ロビンちゃんが帰ってきやしねえかと思ってよ
I wonder where she went... She never even say a word to us.
どこ行ったんだろうな 何も言わずに
I think I'm gonna wander around town looking for her today.
今日は町ん中を捜し回ってみようと思う
I wonder if we'll find her.
見つかるかな？ロビン
Who knows?
さあな
It's not like I have specific places in mind to check,
これといって当てがあるわけじゃねえが
but in any case, she's gotta be here somewhere.
とにかくこの町のどこかにいるのは確かだろ
If something happens, we should rendezvous here at the inn.
もし何かあっても この宿を落ち合い場所にしとこう
I'll help you look for her.
俺も行くぞ　捜しに
Okay. Well, then.
そうか　よし…
Luffy!
ルフィ！
Nami!
ナミさん
I've got bad news.
大変なの
The whole town is talking about it!
今町じゅうこの話で持ちきりで
Luffy! Last night, Mr. Iceburg from the shipyard was...
ルフィ昨日の夜 造船所のアイスバーグさんが！
Mr. Iceburg was shot in his home?!
アイスバーグさんが自宅で撃たれた！？
Hey, cut the crap!
おい！ふざけんな
He was murdered?!
殺されたのか？
Slow down!
いやおい
He isn't the type to make enemies of people!
あの人はそんな人に恨みを買うようなことは…
Wait! Calm down, Paulie!
ちょっと待て！落ち着けパウリー
Listen to me.
とにかく聞け
Look, Mr. Iceburg was found covered in blood in his room this morning.
いいか　アイスバーグさんは今朝 部屋で血まみれになって倒れてるとこを発見されたんだ
He fell into a coma and hasn't come to.
今はまだ昏睡状態で意識はねえが…
Anyway, just get to the office now!
とにかくお前　すぐ本社へ来い
Lulu! Seen Paulie?
ルル！パウリーは？
I just called him. He'll arrive shortly.
今呼んだとこだ　すぐ来る
That so?
そうか
Reporters are making one helluva hullabaloo outside.
外はもう新聞記者が押しかけてきて 大騒ぎじゃ
Pretty ironic considering we're about as out-of-the-loop as they are.
何がどうなっとるか知りたいのは わしらのほうじゃというのに…
Although they tore up the whole office, there's no sign of any money or valuables being stolen.
社内中荒らされてはおるが 金品を盗まれた形跡もない
So if it wasn't a robbery, why would someone just waltz in and gun down Mr. Iceburg?
強盗でもなければ 一体誰が何のためにアイスバーグさんを…
Indeed.
ああ
At any rate, this is a disaster.
しかしえれえことになった
The whole city is in a panic.
町はパニックだぞ
If something were to happen to him...
あの人にもしものことがあったら
Galley-La Company, as well as Water Seven, will be finished.
ガレーラカンパニーも このウォーターセブンもおしまいだ
Doctor... how is he?
先生　いかがでしょう？
Hmm...
んん…
He was shot twice from the front, and thrice from behind.
弾は正面から２発 後ろから３発
I don't know what happened in that room last night, but it was brutal.
ゆうべあの部屋で何が起きたのかは 知らんが　ひどいもんだよ
According to forensic analysis, none of the locks in the building were picked.
鑑識が言うにゃ社内のどこの鍵も 開けられた形跡はないそうだ
The crime occurred in a room no one could have entered.
入れるはずのない部屋で起きた事件
The only thing found in the room was a commonplace mask.
現場で見つかったのは どこにでもありそうな仮面が１つ
Who? Iceboss?
アイスのおっさんが？
They said he's unconscious right now.
今意識不明だって
Everyone loves him. Why...?
あんなにみんなから 慕われてるおっさんが何で…
Who are we talking about, Nami?
誰だいそりゃ　ナミさん
Someone who helped us yesterday.
昨日あたしたちがお世話になった人よ
He runs the shipbuilding company and is mayor of Water Seven.
造船会社の社長で ウォーターセブンの市長
Sounds like an important individual.
そりゃまたずいぶんと大物だな
Yeah.
ええ
For this city, an incident like this is as big as they come.
この町では これ以上ないほどの大事件よ
I'll go check.
ちょっと行ってみる
Wait, Luffy! I'm coming too!
待ってルフィ！あたしも行くから
Well then, let's go look for Robin.
じゃあ　俺らは ロビンちゃんを捜しに行くぞ
What about you?
お前は？
Well...
いや
I'll watch things play out a little longer.
俺はもう少し成り行きを見てる
Extra! Extra! Read all about it!
号外だよ！号外号外！
Water Seven's hero, our mayor, Iceburg, has been assassinated!
ウォーターセブンの英雄市長アイスバーグさんに 暗殺の魔の手が伸びた！
We've got all the breaking news!
事件の続報だよ！
Is Mayor Iceburg okay?
アイスバーグさんは無事なのか？
This is terrible. How could this happen to him?
ひどいわ どうしてこんな目に…
Such a vicious attack... Pirates must've done it!
こんな物騒なマネやらかすのは 海賊どもだろう　やっぱり
I'd sure like for us to catch them!
俺たちでとっ捕まえてやりてえぜ
There were also some pirates who raised hell at Dock One yesterday.
昨日も１番ドックで 暴れたヤツらがいたしな
The Mikazuki gang?!
ミカヅキの一味か？
I suspect the government may be involved.
俺は案外 政府の仕業じゃねえかと思うぜ
Lulu, come again?!
ルル！何を…
I'm talking about Corgi.
コーギーさ
Each time he comes to talk to Mr. Iceburg, he gets turned away.
毎度アイスバーグさんに何か話を持ってきては 突き返されて帰ってく
Franky must be the culprit after all.
やっぱりフランキーが犯人だろ
I don't know what his deal was, but I think Corgi held some undue resentment.
それが何の話かは知らねえが 逆恨みでこんなことを…
Don't carp about the government.
よせ　政府の文句など
If someone hears, it'll cost you dearly.
誰かの耳に入ったら お前もただじゃ済まんぞ
What's the heinous perpetrator's goal? Wealth or power?
許すまじき犯人の目的は 富か権力か！
Who's this assassin who disappeared without a trace?!
足跡も残さず消えた暗殺者は 何者なのか！
Who the hell did it?! They're gonna pay!
どこのどいつだ！ 許さねえぞ絶対！
Thank you for riding the Puffing Tom.
ご乗車ありがとうございました
We'll soon arrive at Blue Station in the City of Water, Water Seven.
間もなく水の都ウォーターセブン ブルーステーション到着でございます
Ah, Paulie!
あっ！パウリーさん
Paulie! Can we get a statement please?!
パウリーさん 今回の事件についてひと言コメントを
Have you been told anything?
どういう連絡を受けてここへ？
Shut up. Get out of my way.
うるせえ　道を空けろ
What explanation did the company give you?
会社のほうからは どのような説明をされたんでしょう？
Please say something!
ひと言お願いします
Are you deaf?! I said to get out of my way!
聞こえなかったのか 道を空けろと言ったんだ
Is Mr. Iceburg in some sort of trouble that might endanger his life?
何か今までにアイスバーグ氏が 命を狙われるような因縁などありませんでしたか？
Anything come to mind?!
思い当たることを何でも！
Any pirate entanglements?!
海賊ともめ事でも？
Paulie! Tell us–
パウリーさん何か…
I said get outta my way!
どけっつってんだろうが！
You dumbasses!
バカ野郎ども！
So he really was attacked.
襲われたってのは やっぱりホントなんだな
Yeah. We may not be able to see him even if we go to the shipyard.
ええ　これじゃあ 造船所に行っても会えないかもね
Then, let's go to his house.
じゃ おっさんの家に行ってみよう
They said his residence is in the main office.
自宅は本社の中にあるんだって
Kiwi... Mozu...
キウイ　モズ
Am I dreaming this?
俺は今夢を見てんのか？
You ain't, Bro...
いいえアニキ
This is, without a doubt, where the Franky House once was.
確かにここは フランキーハウスのあった場所
But this is...
しかしこれはまた…
...just awful.
ずいぶんだわいな
What the hell happened here?!
どうなってんだこりゃ～！
Who did this while I was gone?
誰だ？人の留守中にこんなマネを…
I see. It must be them.
そうか　あいつらだ
How dare you, Straw Hat Luffy?!
おのれ麦わらのルフィ
This is retaliation for stealing your 200 million belly?!
２億ベリーを奪った俺への報復がこれか
How dare you do this to my precious underlings?!
俺のかわいい子分たちをよくも…
So cold-blooded...
無残だわいな
Unforgiveable...!
許さん
Big Bro Franky!
フランキーのアニキ！
You're back!
帰ってきたんですね
Bro!
アニキ！
Oh, you guys are okay? Good.
おう　おめえら無事だったのか よかったぜ
It was real bad. Those guys were insane!
ひどい目に遭いました あいつらもうめちゃくちゃで…
No matter what, you gotta make 'em pay,
俺たちどうしても アニキに敵取ってもらいたくって
so we've been keeping tabs on the Straw Hats' movements.
麦わらたちの動きを探ってました
Where are they?
どこにいるんだ？
We saw them going into an inn.
あいつらが 宿に入るとこ見つけまして…
From there, they headed to Shipyard Island a bit ago.
そこからさっき 造船島のほうへ向かいました
They've gotta be headed to Dock One, same as yesterday.
となりゃきっと昨日いた １番ドックに行ったんですぜ
Okay... I got it!
そうか　分かった
Straw Hat Luffy, this'll be the ass-kicking of your life!
麦わらのルフィ　必ずぶっ潰す
Grandma! Grandma!
ばあちゃん！ばあちゃーん！
The wind is blowing like crazy! Hey, Grandma!
すっごい風だよ！ねえってば！
Crazy wind! Crazy wind! Crazy wind!
–　すごい風！すごい風！ –　ニャー！ニャー！
Tone down the frolicking.
はしゃぐんじゃないよ
It's a southern wind... the caloque, huh?
南の風…　カロックらねえ
The waves are getting rough, too.
波もだいぶ荒れてきた
At this rate, the sea train service will have to be suspended tonight.
今夜には海列車も 運行停止らねえ　こりゃあ
Chimney and Gonbe! Get ready to return to the island!
チムニーゴンベ 島に帰る支度をしな
Okay!
はーい
Aqua Laguna is coming.
アクア･ラグナが来るよ
Attention, please.
お知らせいたします
This is the Water Seven Meteorological Agency.
こちらはウォーターセブン気象予報局
An Aqua Laguna warning has just been issued for the entire island.
ただいま島全域に アクア･ラグナ警報が発令されました
We estimate that it will arrive at Water Seven after midnight tonight.
ウォーターセブン到達は 今夜半過ぎとみられます
Oh, yeah... It's that time of the year.
そうか　もうそんな時期だ
I was preoccupied with the Mayor Iceburg incident.
アイスバーグさんの事件で 頭がいっぱいだったわ
Hey! Aqua Laguna is coming!
おーい アクア･ラグナが来るぞー！
Make sure everyone knows!
聞いてないヤツには知らせてやれ！
Work's over for the day!
仕事は休みにしろ
What's going on?
何だ？
Aqua Laguna?
アクア･ラグナ？
Oh, excuse me.
ああ　おい　ちょっとあんた
What was that broadcast about?
今の放送何なんだ？
You don't know? It's–
“何なんだ”ってそりゃあ…
Oh, are you an out-of-towner?
ああ　あんた旅の人かい
You've come at a bad time.
いやあそりゃ悪い時に来たもんだ
Hm?
ん？
Aqua Laguna is, essentially, a storm surge.
アクア･ラグナってのは つまり高潮のことさ
A storm surge, huh?
高潮か…
That's right. Make sure you evacuate to high ground.
そうだ　ちゃんと高い場所へ 避難しとかねえと
This town will be submerged in the sea.
この町は海につかっちまうぞ
The town will be "submerged"...?
町が…　海に？
Don't worry. It's not going to happen right away.
別に今すぐってわけじゃねえから大丈夫だ
The forecast said it'll be here about midnight.
予報じゃ今日の夜中だとさ
Well, this happens every year. Be careful!
まあ毎年のことだ　気ぃつけなよ
Okay.
ああ
It'll be submerged in the sea?
海につかるって…
What?! This place will sink?!
えっ！ここ沈むのか？
Sounds like it. At any rate, let's hurry and find Robin.
そうらしいな とにかく急いでロビンちゃんを捜そう
All right.
うん
Please tell us something!
何か教えて
Mr. Iceburg!
アイスバーグさん！
What the hell happened?!
何があったんだ…
What's going on?!
どうなってるの？
We can't enter, huh?
入れねえか
Either way, we've gotta see Iceboss again somehow.
どのみちもいっかい会わなきゃ なんねえんだよな　アイスのおっさんには
Excuse me. Do you know where the entrance to the main office is?
ねえ　すいません 本社の入り口って分かりますか？
Oh, that's not happening.
ああ　無駄だぞ
You can enter through Dock One, but only concerned parties and certain reporters are allowed in.
１番ドックの中から入るんだが中には関係者か 特定の記者たちしか入れねえんだ
Everyone's anxious to find out how he's doing, but we can't do a thing.
心配で居ても立ってもいられねえのは みんなおんなじさ
I see... Thanks.
そう…　ありがとう
What's all the commotion? Pretty crowded.
何の騒ぎだこりゃあ わらわらと…
Well, the bigger the audience, the better.
まあ　観客は多いほうがいいか
Ah! This beat...
このリズムは！
It can't be... Not him!
まさか！そんなバカな！
Why at a time like this?!
何でこんな時に！
Hey, you guys! Did you just call my name?!
ヘイお前たち！ 俺の名を今呼んだのか？
We didn't! Go away!
呼んでねえよ！ どっか行け！
Where?! Where is he?!
–　どこだ！？どこにいる！？ –　どっから来んだ？
Ahh! He's over there!
ああっ！あそこだ！
He's here!
出たー！
Yow! Yow! Yow!
アウ！アウ！アウ！
♪ Come now, don't be shy, ask me my name! ♪
恥ずかしがらずに聞いてみな俺の名を
We don't wanna ask! Get lost!
–　聞きたくねえ –　消えろ！
You attacked Mayor Iceburg, didn't you?!
アイスバーグさんを 襲ったのはお前だろ！
– What?! He did it?! – It's gotta be him!
–　えっあいつが？ –　そうに決まってる
Get off this island!
この島から出ていけ！
You should be sent to the gallows, punk!
縛り首だこのチンピラ！
Ugh... shut up, you flies!
あ～　うるせえハエどもめ
♪ I'm this island's number-one super guy! ♪
俺はこの島イチのスーパーな男
♪ The face of the Water Seven underworld! ♪
ウォーターセブンの裏の顔
♪ That's right! People call me... Wow! ♪
そうだ俺は人呼んでワーオ！
Franky!
フランキー！
Show yourself, Straw Hat!
出てこい麦わら！
You must be here, Straw Hat Luffy!
ここにいるはずだ 麦わらのルフィ！
What the heck?! That pervy guy called my name!
何だ？あの変態野郎 俺の名前を呼んだぞ
Didn't people call him Franky just now?
今みんな“フランキー”って 呼んでなかった？
It's him!
あいつが…
He's the one who beat up Usopp!
あいつがウソップを…
This money belongs to us now.
この金はもう俺たちのもんだわ！
Give it... back.
返…　せ
Give it baaaaaack!
返してくれーっ！
It's him...!
あいつが！
Luffy?
ルフィ？
Hey, bikini bottoms!
おい！海水パンツ！
Luffy!
ルフィ！
Huh?
あん？
I'm Luffy!
俺がルフィだ
– There's no information available? C'mon... – What's going on?
–　おい何の情報もないのかよ –　どうなったんですか？
Everyone...
皆さん
Kalifa...
カリファ…
Please enter the room... quietly.
静かに… 部屋へ入ってください
What...? Then...!
えっあ…　じゃあ…
Mr. Iceburg...
アイスバーグさんが
just regained consciousness.
たった今　意識を取り戻しました
– That's great!
–　よかった！
I could leap for joy!
ホントによかった！
Mr. Iceburg!
アイスバーグさん！
Well, sorry for worrying you...
ンマー心配かけた
In any case, I'm glad you're alive!
とにかく命があってよかったぜ
Please focus on resting up.
ゆっくりお休みんなって…
We'll take care of stuff at the shipyard.
造船所のことは俺たちで何とかしますんで
I need to tell you... about the culprits who broke into my room last night...
ところでゆうべ俺の部屋に 侵入してきた犯人だが…
Uh... They're still investigating.
あ… それならまだ捜査中で…
Good, but I remember it.
いや　覚えてる
Wha...?
えっ？
– What?
え…
There were two. One was a big man wearing a mask.
２人いた １人は仮面をかぶった大男
The other was...
もう１人は―
a tall woman with long, black hair.
黒髪で長身の女
There's no mistaking it. Those black eyes belong to...
間違いない あの黒い瞳は…
Mayor Iceburg...
アイスバーグさん…
Mayor Iceburg regained consciousness!
アイスバーグさんの意識が戻ったぞー！
– Is that true?! – All right!
–　やったー！
– Great! – Hooray!
–　よかった！
So you're the one they call... Straw Hat Luffy?!
おめえか！麦わらのルフィってのは！
You went on quite the rampage while I was gone, didn't you?
人の留守中にえらく大暴れ してくれたじゃないのお兄ちゃん
When I got back, I couldn't believe my eyes...
帰ってきて目を疑ったぜ俺ァ
Well, my house is totally unrecognizable.
いやいや見事に 原形ないんだもんな俺の家がよ
And how dare you treat my underlings so cruelly?
子分どももまあ ひどい目に遭わせてくれやがって
I can't take it anymore.
もうダメだ俺
No one can stop me this week!
今週の俺はもうホントに止められねえ
Nothing you say will matter.
何を言っても
I won't calm down until I rip you to shreds!
おめえをボロ雑巾のようにするまでは この怒りは収まらねえ！
Hey, you!
ちょっと！
Hm?
あ？
Yeah, you! What'd you do with our 200 million belly?!
あんたあたしたちのお金 どうしたの！２億ベリー！
Give it back to us!
返しなさいよ！
Huh?! 200 million belly?!
あ？２億ベリーだあ？
I already spent it! It's completely gone!
そんなもん使っちまって もうカラッケツよ
You obviously stole that money from somewhere.
どこぞで奪ってきた金を
You've got no room to get all uppity with me, pirates!
偉そうに守ろうとするんじゃねえ海賊が！
It doesn't matter.
そんなのはいい
Hm?
ん？
Not true! Money does matter!
よくないわよお金は！
At any rate, I won't be happy...
とにかく俺はお前を
until I kick your ass!
ぶっ飛ばさねえと気が済まねえ！
Hmph.
フン！
No, I won't be happy, you bastard!
気が済まねえのはこっちだバカ野郎！
Hey! Come down here already!
おい！ さっさとこっちへ下りてこい！
Whoa! This is it! Franky's about to rampage!
わっ！もうダメだ フランキーが暴れだすぞ！
Evacuate! Everyone, evacuate!
避難しろ！ みんなも避難しろ！
Get out of here!
逃げろー！
What's he doing?
何してんの？あれ
He shot fire out of his mouth!
口から火ぃ吹いた！
What is he?!
何者なの？あいつ！
You've never seen anyone breathe fire before?
火ぃ吹くのが珍しいか？
Hey, he might have devil fruit powers.
ねえ　ひょっとしたら能力者かもよ
Then, what fruit?
じゃ何の実だ！？
What's with him? He jumped in the water!
何だ？あの野郎 水に飛び込みやがった
Is he stupid? If he ate a devil fruit, he'll drown!
バカか？悪魔の実食ってたら 溺れて終わりだぞ
He must've slipped and fallen! He definitely has a fire breath power.
きっと滑って落ちたのよ 火を吹く能力者よあいつ！
What the heck?! He can swim?!
何だあいつ！泳げんのか！？
No!
いやーっ！
I didn't eat a devil fruit!
悪魔の実なんざ食っちゃいねえよ！
Gum-Gum...
ゴムゴムの…
I've heard about your power.
聞いてるぜ　お前の能力
Strong Right!
ストロングライト！
What the...?
何？
Luffy!
ルフィ！
Luffy! Luffy!
ルフィ！ルフィ！
What...? What was that?
何？今のは何なの？
Oh...? You guys didn't know?
ああ？知らなかったのかい？ お姉ちゃんたち
Well then, I'll tell you.
じゃあ教えとこうか
I'm a modified human.
俺は改造人間
A cyborg!
サイボーグだ
One of the Straw Hats?
麦わらの一味だと？
Is that true?
本当か？その話
Yes. My own investigation led to the same conclusion.
ええ 犯人の名前は私の調べでも…
I just had Lucci confirm it with the government. So you see...
今ルッチに政府に確認を取ってもらったわ そしたら…
Yeah... When I contacted the government, they said she's one of the Straw Hats.
ああ　政府に連絡を取ったら 麦わらの一味の仲間だと言われたクルッポー！
Then... they, the Straw Hats, don't have a leg to stand on.
じゃあ犯人はあいつら… 麦わらの一味ということになるのう
What the hell?!
何だってんだ
Is this because we wouldn't fix their ship?!
船が直らねえことの腹いせか？
Hard to say.
それは分からん
But no matter the reason, the truth is we have them dead to rights.
じゃが理由はどうあれ ヤツらの仕業じゃということだけは…
We can learn their motive after they're hogtied.
訳なんざあいつらを ふんじばって聞きゃあいい
I don't know what you're thinking,
どういう言い分があるのかは知らねえが
but you'll pay for this, Straw Hat!
この落とし前きっちりと つけさせてもらうぜ麦わら！
Hey! There's trouble!
おーい！大変だ！
– You're too loud, Tilestone!
–　声がでけえよタイルストン！
How rude! All of you, be quiet!
無礼者！ みんなおとなしくしなさい！
Oh, Mr. Iceburg!
おおっ！アイスバーグさん！
I'm really glad you came around!
気がついてホントによかったぜ！
You yell every damn word you say!
うるせえなおめえはいちいち
It's not good for him, got it?!
容体に響くだろ！
Yeah! You're right! I'm sorry!
うおー　そうだなすまん！
Oh, that's right! There's trouble! Listen, you guys!
そうだ！大変なんだい 聞いてくれ！
Don't come inside the room. Speak from where you are.
部屋に入るな　そこから話せ
That pirate Straw Hat from yesterday started a fight with Franky at Dock One,
１番ドックで今昨日来た麦わらの海賊が フランキーとケンカを始めやがって
and they're wrecking the shipyard!
造船所がめちゃくちゃに！うおー！
Straw Hat...
麦わら…
Mr. Iceburg!
アイスバーグさん！
That bastard...! He's got some nerve showing his face at the dock!
あの野郎 よくもてめえからノコノコと…
Please get some rest, Mr. Iceburg.
少しお休みくださいアイスバーグさん
I'll be here by your side.
私がそばについていますから
...Pistol!
ピストル！
Watch out! It's coming down!
危ない！倒れるぞ！
The ship is breaking apart!
船が壊れる！
Stop it! This fight is crazy!
うっ　やめろ！ 何ちゅう戦いをするんだ！
Luffy! Beat up that bikini bastard!
ルフィ！ぶっ飛ばすのよ！ そんな海水パンツ！
Bro!
アニキ！
Give him a good fight!
ファイトだわいなー！
Anyway, your ass... is as good as kicked!
とにかくお前は… ぶっ飛ばしてやるからな！
Then kick it if you can! Your attacks don't work on me!
やってみろ！ おめえの攻撃なんざ効きやしねえよ！
Weapons Left!
ウエポンズレフト！
Gum-Gum...
ゴムゴムの…
Whip!
ムチ！
What the heck?! What happened?!
何だ？何が起こったんだ？
Ah! That's...!
あっ！あれは！
Who was that?!
誰だ！
You've got some gall pulling this crap! What's your goal, Straw Hat?!
くだらねえマネしてくれたな！ お前の狙いは何だ？麦わら！
Galley-La... What do you want?
ガレーラ　何の用だ？
It's the Dock One foremen!
１番ドックの職長たちだ！
All right! The foremen are finally here!
やったー！ やっと職長たちが来てくれたぞ！
That was close! The shipyard is practically destroyed!
危ねえ危ねえ　もう少しで 造船所が大破されちまうとこだったぞ
Thank goodness! They're the shipwrights we met yesterday!
よかった！ 昨日の船大工の人たちじゃない
They're on our side, right?
こっちの味方よね！
Hey now, you Galley-La blowhards!
おうおう ガレーラの兄ちゃんたち
You shouldn't butt into our fight!
人のケンカに首突っ込んでくれたら 困るじゃない
Do you wanna get hurt?
ケガしてえのか？
It's amazing you'd say that.
ようそんな口利けるもんじゃ
Leveling our factory is reason enough to make you pay the piper!
うちの工場をこれだけ荒らされれば 理由がなくても止めに来るわい
He's right, Franky! How're you gonna settle this?!
うおー！そうだフランキー てめえこの落とし前どうつける気だ！
Hold on a sec, Tilestone. We'll talk about it later.
ちょっと待てタイルストン その話は後でつけよう
We have more important business right now.
今はもっと重要な用事があるはずだぜ
Right, Straw Hat Luffy?
なあ麦わらのルフィ
You know what I'm talking about.
身に覚えがあるだろう
I'm surprised you'd show your face here again.
よくまたここへ顔を出せたもんだ
What? Why? We came here because we heard the news about Iceboss.
えっ何で… 俺たちおっさんのニュース聞いて…
Oh, my family wasn't enough, so you messed with Galley-La, too?
ハァ～　うちの一家じゃ事足りず ガレーラにもちょっかい出してたのか？
Are you just some pubescent punks who piss off everyone you come across?!
てめえら一味は 触れるものみんな傷つける思春期か？
Like I said, we didn't do anything!
だから！ 俺たちは何にもしてねえよ！
Play dumb, and we'll just put the screws to you!
とぼけるなら締め上げるまでだ！
Rope Action Half-Knot!
ロープアクション　ハーフノット！
I can't breathe... I can't breathe...!
苦しい…　苦し…
Air... Drive!
エア　ドライブ！
You sons of bitches! Don't you know what "don't interfere" means?!
この野郎ども！ 邪魔すんなっつったのが分かんねえのか！
I'm the one with a grudge against him!
そいつに恨みがあんのは俺だー！
Beat 'em up, Galley-La Company!
やっちまえ！ ガレーラカンパニー！
The company's furious five are fighting!
社内最強の５人のケンカだー！
Wait, what? Why are the shipwrights fighting us too?!
えっ！？えっ！？ 何で船大工も敵なのよ！
It's heating up.
うずうず
Hey! Wait! I haven't got the slightest reason to fight you guys!
おい　待てって 俺はお前らとケンカする理由が少しもない！
He's... got devil fruit powers?
こいつ…　能力者か
Hey, are you bastards even listening?!
あのなあおめえら 人の話聞いてんのか！
I said...
そいつは…
he's my prey!
俺の獲物だと言ってんだろうが！
Hm?
ん？
We don't have time to trifle with you, Franky!
お前につきおうとる暇はないんじゃ フランキー！
What'd you say, you wild monkey?!
何をこの山ザルが！
You're the one who's interfering, Franky!
お前こそ邪魔だフランキー！
That's our Tilestone! He's as mighty as ever!
タイルストンさすがだ！ 相変わらずの超怪力じゃねえか！
You jerk! Stop it!
この…　やめろ！
These guys are tough!
ホントに強えなこいつら
Dammit! What's with you?! At least tell me why you're doing this!
クソッ　何なんだ！ 理由ぐらい言え！
Straw Hat, we're the ones who'd like to know why.
麦わら 理由を知りたいのは俺たちのほうだ
Last night, intruders broke into our main office and attacked Mr. Iceburg.
ゆうべ本社に侵入して アイスバーグさんを襲撃した犯人は
It was you guys! Admit it!
お前らだろうが！
Can't be... This can't be...
そんな…　そんなことが
They messed with my fight anyway.
こいつら人のケンカに…
That was... without a doubt, Nico Robin.
あの姿… 間違いなくニコ･ロビンだった
Was that big guy with her also one of the Straw Hats?
横にいた大男も麦わらの一味なのか？
Why did they attack me in the first place?
そもそもヤツらは 何の意味があって俺を襲ったんだ？
It's hard to imagine that they did it as payback for yesterday.
昨日の腹いせとは考えにくい
They must be after something of mine.
狙いはやはり俺の持ち物だろう
Then, are those pirates connected to the government?
だとすればあの海賊たちと 政府がつながっているのか？
Or could they really be after...?
それとも単独であれを狙って…
Straw Hat...
麦わら…
Breaking news! Breaking news!
特報！特報だー！
From what Mayor Iceburg has said, the culprits have been identified!
アイスバーグさんの証言から 犯人が割れたぞ！
What?! Is that true?!
ええ！ホントか！
Let the entire city know immediately and corner the bastards!
早く町じゅうに知らせて 犯人たちを追い込もう！
Don't let them leave Water Seven!
このウォーターセブンから逃がすな！
Capture them!
犯人を捕まえろ！
The culprits who attacked Mr. Iceburg are...
アイスバーグ氏襲撃事件の犯人は…
the Straw Hat Pirates!
海賊　麦わらの一味だ！
Iceburg was attacked? What're you talking about?
アイスバーグが？何の話だ？
Wh-What do they mean?
な…　何よそれ
D... Don't be ridiculous! Why... Why would we do such a thing?!
バ…　バカ言え！何で… 何で俺たちがそんなことするんだ！
When Mr. Iceburg came around, he told us that he remembered the two who did it.
犯人を２人覚えていると 目を覚ましたアイスバーグさんが証言したんだ
One was a big man wearing a mask.
１人は仮面をかぶった大男
The other was a tall woman.
もう１人が長身の女
When we asked the government, they confirmed her affiliation with you:
政府に聞きゃあこの女 おめえらの仲間だと言うじゃねえか
Nico Robin, the woman with a bounty on her head!
ニコ･ロビンって賞金首はよ！
Robin?!
ロビン！？
Did you come to this island as part of a plot to kill Mr. Iceburg?
初めっからアイスバーグさんの命を 狙ってこの島に来たのか
Or did you decide to do it after you guys met him yesterday?
それとも昨日お前らがあの方に会った後 そんな気を起こしたのか
I don't know how you pirates think...
海賊の考えることなんざ分からねえがな
but since we know you're guilty, there's no way we let you walk free.
犯人と分かった以上 お前らを野放しにゃしねえ
So he's one of the culprits?
あいつが犯人なのか
We'll make him pay! We have to!
許せねえ… 絶対許せねえ！
Oh, no!
そんな…
So, hey, did Iceburg die or didn't he?
おいおい　それで アイスバーグのヤツは死んだのか？
As if a bunch of halfwits could even kill him.
こんなバカどもに殺されてたまるか！
As long as this punk lives, he could go after Mr. Iceburg again.
生きているからこそまた アイスバーグさんの命を狙いかねないこいつを
So we'll take care of him right here, right now.
ここで始末するんだ
It says "dead or alive."
デッド･オア･アライブ
They want you either way.
“生死を問わず”
Do you know what it means to be a wanted man?
指名手配の意味が分かるか？
You pirates can't complain, no matter who does what to you.
お前たち海賊は 誰に何をされても文句は言えん
In other words, the world's laws won't protect you guys.
世界の法は お前たちを守らんということじゃ
That's right.
そうだ
We're outlaws.
俺たちは無法者だ
I know that. But...
分かってるよ　だけどな
don't talk crap about Robin when you know nothing about her!
お前らロビンのことを何にも知らねえくせに 勝手なこと言うな！
Luffy...
ルフィ…
Let me see Iceboss!
アイスのおっさんに会わせてくれ
I'm sure he's mistaken! There's no way it was Robin!
見間違いだそんなの ロビンなわけがねえ！
Why would we let you get closer when we can't ascertain your intentions?!
何をしでかすか分からねえヤツを アイスバーグさんに近づけられるか！
He's right! Tie 'em up!
そうだ！犯人を縛り上げろ！
They tried to kill our hero!
この町の英雄を殺そうとしたヤツらだ！
Send them to the gallows!
縛り首にしろ！
H-Hey! What're you saying?!
ちょっと！何なのよ！
You bitch!
このっ
Hey! You were with that Straw Hat guy earlier, weren't you?
おい娘　お前さっき 麦わらのあいつと一緒にいただろう
You must be one of them, too!
お前も仲間だな？
Is that right?!
ホントかい？
Yeah, he's right! I saw her too!
そう　そうよ 私も見たわよこの女！
We're not gonna let you get away!
逃がしゃしないよ！
Stop resisting!
ジタバタするんじゃないよ！
Hey, cut it out!
ちょっとやめてよ！
Nami!
ナミ！
The news is already making its way through the city.
情報はすぐ町じゅうに広がる
You have nowhere to run!
もう逃げ場はねえ
We'll bring down each and every one of you!
一味全員　俺たちがしとめてやる
Extra! Extra!
号外！号外！
The Straw Hat Pirates are the prime suspects in the attempt on Mr. Iceburg's life!
アイスバーグ氏襲撃事件の犯人は 海賊　麦わらの一味！
We at the Hydro City Sentinel will pay for any information on their whereabouts!
一味全員の目撃情報は 水水新聞社が買い取らせていただきます！
The culprits are on this island!
犯人はこの島にいる！
Find the Straw Hats and send them all to the gallows!
麦わらの一味を捜して 全員縛り首にしろ！
Yeah!
–　おー！